This is weird.
Captain Zhao sure likes to keep us all in the dark about the case.
He just said to keep watch.
What the hell could be going on?
Lu Guang, the guy in the ward, and Cheng Xiaoxie, the guy who just left.
Well, rumor has it they've got some kind of weird skill?
Right, not just them.
There's something unusual about the criminal too.
I believe it's somebody who can possess people, like they can take over bodies.
That's why we need to look out for odd behavior.
Hey, you guys aren't possessed, are you?
How can I know for sure?
Wait, was it okay to leave Lu Guang alone?
If he got possessed, that'd be bad.
Nah, we're good.
We checked for dangerous items.
He's safe.
And besides, he didn't want us in there anyway.
Mr. Lu, are you alright?
Damn it, it's locked!
Then break it down!
Secure the room right now!
I'll report in!
Captain Zhao!
He's disappeared!
Lu Guang's gone.
What happened?
We went inside, and the window was out.
We thought that maybe he had an accident.
We've secured the room, but he's not here.
Call for backup and start pulling surveillance footage from the area.
Find him now!
He couldn't have just vanished.
Was it another person with powers?
What in the world is happening here?
Officer Wang!
You in here?
Captain Zhao?
No one's here.
They're gone.
It's Wang Juan.
She took them.
I'm going after her.
She took them?
But why?
It doesn't make sense.
Where would she go?
No time to wonder.
First, we get them back.
Then, we find some answers.
Hey, Liu.
Did you see where Wang Juan went?
Huh?
Yeah, she was just here.
There.
They went across the street.
If you hurry, you might still be able to catch up with her.
Liu!
Call for backup now!
Yes, sir!
Tell them to set up road blocks!
No vehicles allowed to leave!
Wang Juan!
Zhang Xiaoxi!
Captain Zhao!
Sir, I'm over here!
What's your ID?
7-7-4-5-0.
Why did you take them?
I...
I can't remember.
We were just outside the restrooms.
What was that?
Speak up.
I knew you would try to break the boss of mine.
I just wish you would have been smarter about it.
Ugh.
One more time.
I said...
You showed up right after we left the room.
And you knew the exact reason why I asked to leave.
So who else is listening, officer?
Sorry.
That's all I can remember.
And then I ended up here.
Already handcuffed.
All I could do was watch as they ran away.
Backup is on the way.
Stay here and coordinate with them.
Any idea where they might be headed?
Wait!
The bug we put on Zhang Xiaoxi also has a tracker.
So don't let her know that you're wired or she'll shut down.
Right.
Let's get you bugged, okay?
I'm going after them.
Take my phone so we can stay in contact.
Hello?
Captain, where are you?
I'm…
Chao Ling.
It's Officer Wang.
Captain Xiao's in pursuit.
He left his phone with me.
He did?
I guess I can trust you then.
Do you know what's going on?
Where's Zhang Xiaoxi?
I'm at the station.
Where are you?
Chao Ling.
Right now you need to stay calm and stay put.
Things just got worse.
Officer Wang!
Is there a problem here?
Excuse me.
Have you seen Officer Wang?
She just left with two other people to get dinner.
Can you tell me what's going on?
Why does Captain Xiao need me to call for backup?
Hey, where are you going?
Remember, in a perfect world, it should only take you eight minutes to get to the old town.
And police reinforcements should take about twenty minutes.
So you do have a bit of a window.
Just be aware that you have a heart out at 7.20.
Of course, I'll also have something in place for any on-foot pursuers.
I expect we'll have some over-eager detectives to delay.
Lookie here.
Found us a lost little babe.
Find us a lost little babe.
Dammit!
Did I lose this signal?
I...
The signal's fine.
So why haven't they moved?
What are they doing?
Yeah, I figured as much.
Why do you make it so hard to trust you?
This thing?
It just spoils the game.
Yeah, you're right.
Sorry.
It won't happen again.
Police! Stand aside!
That's not happening.
I'm here for one reason.
And that's to keep you where you are.
I'm here.
No, no, no!
Not again!
Girls aren't supposed to be this hard to take down!
It's not fair!
Just let me kill you!
I can't screw this up!
Not again!
I don't want to die!
No!
Ahh!
Hahaha!
Huh!
Hmm?
Huh?
Huh!
Ahh!
Ohh!
Stop!
They're already long gone.
You should be more worried about that police woman that you left behind.
Stop! You don't need to break anything else tonight! I get it! I'm done now!
Just cuff me and take me back to the station before my boss finds up and lays me, okay?
Stand up!
Oh, hey boss. What did you think of my acting there?
Pretty convincing, huh?
Fix your mask.
You just had one job to do. So what happened?
That lady cop was a lot tougher than she looks, boss!
Yes, I know. She was tough back then, too.
Shame. Wish she hadn't seen your face.
She really was something else.
Hongxuan.
Oh, oh, my god.
Oh.
Here lay back then.
elderlyindustry.
Oh, my god.
Oh!
All according to plan.
Chou Chousha!
Get away from her!
I'm impressed she managed to catch up to us. Not that it matters, though. Now come on. We mustn't leave our boat waiting.
Chou Chousha! Hey!
Ahh...
Oh, God, right on time.